<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chromagotchi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chromagotchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>SWE Group 18: Clara Fee, Via Liu, John Otto, Laya Yalamanchili</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:40:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bug fixes and improvements</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/bug-fixes-and-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/bug-fixes-and-improvements/</guid>
      <description>Update: bug fixes and improvements 🐛We heard your feedback: below is a list of our most recent bug fixes and improvements!🐛 Version 2.1.4 Bug Fixes&#xA;Fixed Audio Dropout Issue: Resolved a problem where users experienced intermittent audio dropouts during live streaming. Corrected Metadata Display: Addressed an issue causing the currently playing song metadata (artist, title) to display incorrectly or lag. Stability Improvements in Low Connectivity: Enhanced the app&amp;rsquo;s stability when operating under low network connectivity conditions, reducing crashes and buffering delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customization update: fireplace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/customization-update-fireplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/customization-update-fireplace/</guid>
      <description>Customization update: fireplace 🔥 We heard your feedback: fireplace visual display options added! 🔥 The team at RadioPlayer is hard at work implementing new features to build listenership, allowing for greater functionality for users and broadcasters alike.&#xA;A fireplace visual display option was just added! Choose between a looping video of a fireplace, a YouTube livestream of a fireplace, or a many other static image choices. As always, if you don&amp;rsquo;t like our options, feel free to upload your own!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New feature: Phone it in!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/new-feature-phone-it-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/post/new-feature-phone-it-in/</guid>
      <description>New Feature: Phone it in! ☎️ We heard your feedback: calling in is here! ☎️ The team at RadioPlayer is hard at work implementing new features to build listenership, allowing for greater functionality for users and broadcasters alike.&#xA;With the Phone It In feature, RadioPlayer users will be able to &amp;ldquo;call in&amp;rdquo; at any time during your radio broadcast. Users can send in song requests, answer questions in a Q&amp;amp;A format, or even participate in a live talk show!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Blog Post] Chromagotchi Development Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/clara-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/clara-blog/</guid>
      <description>Chromagotchi Development Journey: Design Decisions, Mistakes, Lessons Learned By Clara Fee&#xA;This blog post details my perspective on the Chromagotchi development process. I attempt to explore the various design and functionality decisions we made while developing the extension, focusing particularly on the reasoning behind these decisions as well as the lessons we learned during the process.&#xA;Ideation In the initial ideation phase, we decided that we wanted to make a tool that helped users improve their productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Blog Post] Post-Mortem Analysis: Lessons from Developing Chromagotchi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/laya-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/laya-blog/</guid>
      <description>Post-Mortem Analysis: Lessons from Developing Chromagotchi By Laya Yalamanchili&#xA;In developing our Chromagotchi chrome extension, we balanced functionality, aesthetics, and user interaction. This post-mortem analysis aims to dissect the decisions, challenges, and lessons learned from our project, focusing on the evolution from our initial proposal to the final implementation.&#xA;The Balancing Act: Functionality vs. Aesthetics Initially, our project proposal envisioned a Chrome extension that would motivate users to minimize their time on distracting websites by nurturing a digital pet akin to a Tamagotchi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Demo Video] Chromagotchi Demo Video</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/demo-vid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/page/demo-vid/</guid>
      <description>Chromagotchi Demo Video Click here to view our Demo Video for Chromagotchi, made by our developer Via Liu!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Made with ❤️ by the Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&#xA;We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact To get into contact with us, report bugs or issues, or suggest features for new version of Chromagotchi, reach out to us at any of these emails:&#xA;cfee3@brynmawr.edu&#xA;bangchel@sas.upenn.edu&#xA;layay@wharton.upenn.edu&#xA;jwotto@wharton.upenn.edu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/chromagotchi-landing-page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.&#xA;Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The server hosting this site can collect the following information:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
